{
    "subject": "resource/Caught_in_the_Rain",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1910s_comedy_films",
    "human_readable": "Caught in the Rain is a comedy film of the 1910s.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8988661170005798,
            "question": "Is 'Caught in the Rain' a drama or a comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7153157591819763,
            "question": "What decade was the film 'Caught in the Rain' released in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7113792896270752,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Caught in the Rain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6638027429580688,
            "question": "Can you name some famous comedy films from the 1910s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4217541813850403,
            "question": "Can you think of any modern comedies that share similarities with films from the 1910s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40730318427085876,
            "question": "Who were some popular actors or directors working in film during the 1910s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1402028650045395,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in comedy films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09621809422969818,
            "question": "What are some characteristics that define a classic comedy film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07696127891540527,
            "question": "How did technology influence the development of comedy films in the early 20th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06783754378557205,
            "question": "Why do people continue to enjoy watching older comedy films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Caught in the Rain is a comedy film of the 1910s.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3471_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did technology influence the development of comedy films in the early 20th century?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3471_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics that define a classic comedy film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3471_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in comedy films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3471_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3471_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3471_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3471_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3471_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3471_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3471_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3471_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3471_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3471_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3471_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about \"Caught in the Rain,\" indicating it was Chaplin's first film where he directed and starred, and that it was produced in 1914. Given this context, it can be inferred that \"Caught in the Rain\" is indeed a comedy film from the 1910s."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}